	Amber Nash 510.612.3733 nash.beram@gmail.com GitHub annnash88 LinkedIn ambernash Academic and nonprofit administrator turned developer. Building programs that center user experience, pulling inspiration from community needs.
PROJECTS	Proficient → Ruby, Sinatra, Rails, ActiveRecord, SQL, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax, HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Materialize, RSPEC, Jasmine, Git, Heroku, MVC, OOP, agile development Exposure → Swift, Android, Java, Adobe InDesign, WordPress
2017 – present	SANCTUARY – Provides immigrant community with tools to protect themselves from/during ICE (Immigration & Customs Enforcement) Raids. Role: Project Lead, Swift/iOS dev, Twilio API, design. → sanctuaryapp.herokuapp.com
	 Users can map and track ICE sightings in their communities A panic button allows users to instantly send alert-text to 5 contacts After selecting the panic button, the user is directed to a list of their rights Website is fully translated into both English and Spanish
2017 - present	REMIX-IT – Allows users to create and send music to friends. Recipients can contribute to the recording, creating their own remix. Role: solo-project.
2017 - present	HAND UP – Web app helping non-profits find resources, volunteers, and funds. 2-person team. Role: Front-end developer.
EMPLOYMENT	
2014 – 2016	 FAMILY FINDING COORDINATOR – SENECA FAMILY OF AGENCIES + Supported 6+ professionals, facilitating 25+ new relationships internationally, resulting in meaningful revenue increases. + Worked with 40+ public and private child welfare orgs, and government agencies + Updated web content, branding, and coordinated with offsite developers + Redesigned department and educational marketing materials. + Member of the Diversity and Inclusion (D&I) Action Board and Steering Committee. Contributed to the employee handbook by writing sections of their D&I curriculum.
2012 – 2014	 CLINIC COORDINATOR – STRATEGIES FOR LEARNING + Managed office operations, created promotional materials, + Maintained, updated, and expanded company website using WordPress. + Oversaw expansion through assisting in client outreach, and facilitating relationships between other educational organizations within the Bay Area.
2010 – 2012	 ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT – JEWISH UNITED FUND + Supported the campaign department by facilitating event logistics for large community events - 500+ participants. + Maintained client records and entered corporate contacts into in-house CMS system + Created reports tracking Chicago's most profitable financial institutions to generate new donors.
EDUCATION	
201 <i>7</i> 2015 2010	DEV BOOTCAMP → San Francisco, CA, Full Stack Web Development Immersive PACIFIC SCHOOL OF RELIGION → Berkeley, CA, Master of Theological Studies MILLS COLLEGE → OAKLAND, CA, Bachelor of Arts - History